Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm microfilm Accounting Department records, 1942-1954 RL.11717
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm microfilm Accounting Department records
1942-1954
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.11717
3.0 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York. Collection includes lists of cancelled checks, petty cash vouchers and invoices, summaries of advertising production expenses and labor costs and other financial data. Main JWT offices represented include New York, Chicago, Detroit, Los Angeles and San Francisco. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: Checks Cancelled; Petty Cash; Production Billing
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York.
Beginning in the 1930s, documents from several JWT departments and functions were microfilmed, including Legal Department, Treasurer's Office, As Broadcast Scripts and Commercials for Radio and Television, Investigations, Publicity Department, Artwork, Consumer Panel, and Radio/Television Department. Documents were microfilmed in no order, and typed and hand-written indices were produced for the microfilms. It is believed that once microfilmed, most of the original documents were destroyed.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm microfilm Accounting Department records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1987.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
J. Walter Thompson Company. Alun Jones papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Corporate documentation
J. Walter Thompson Company. Edward G. Wilson papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Glen Dell papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Treasurer's Office records
Collection Overview
Collection includes lists of cancelled checks, petty cash vouchers and invoices, summaries of advertising production expenses and labor costs and other financial data. Main JWT offices represented include New York, Chicago, Detroit, Los Angeles and San Francisco. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising; Advertising agencies; Advertising -- United States -- Costs; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; J. Walter Thompson Company -- History; J. Walter Thompson Company -- Management
- Checks Cancelled, 1949-1952; 1
  - Checks cancelled, 1949 (Reel 954)
    Scope and Contents
    Irving Trust Feb.-June
  - Checks cancelled, 1949 (Reel 955)
    Irving Trust June-Oct.
  - Checks cancelled, 1949 (Reel 956)
    Irving Trust Oct.-Dec.; tab checks Jan.-Feb.
  - Checks cancelled, 1949 (Reel 957)
    Tab checks Feb.-May
  - Checks cancelled, 1949 (Reel 958)
    Tab checks May-Sept.
  - Checks cancelled, 1949 (Reel 959)
    Tab checks Sept.-Dec.
  - Checks cancelled, 1949-1950 (Reel 960)
    Irving Trust 1950 Mar.; tab checks 1949 Dec.
  - Checks cancelled, 1950 (Reel 948)
    Irving Trust Mar.-Aug.
  - Checks cancelled, 1950 (Reel 949)
    Irving Trust Aug.-Dec.
  - Checks cancelled, 1950 (Reel 950)
    Irving Trust Dec.; tab checks Jan.-Mar.
  - Checks cancelled, 1950 (Reel 951)
    Tab checks Mar.-June
  - Checks cancelled, 1950 (Reel 952)
    Tab checks June-Sept.
  - Checks cancelled, 1950 (Reel 953)
    Tab checks Sept.-Nov.
  - Checks cancelled, 1950-1951 (Reel 947)
    Irving Trust 1950 Jan.-Mar.; tab checks 1951 Nov.-Dec.
  - Checks cancelled, 1951 (Reel 941)
    Irving Trust Mar.-July
  - Checks cancelled, 1951 (Reel 942)
    Irving Trust July-Oct.
  - Checks cancelled, 1951 (Reel 943)
  - Checks cancelled, 1951 (Reel 944)
    Tab checks Feb.-June
  - Checks cancelled, 1951 (Reel 945)
  - Checks cancelled, 1951 (Reel 946)
  - Checks cancelled, 1951-1952 (Reel 940)
    Irving Trust; tab checks
  - Checks cancelled, 1952 (Reel 933)
    Irving Trust regular and branch banks Jan.-Apr.
  - Checks cancelled, 1952 (Reel 934)
    Irving Trust regular and branch banks Apr.-Sept.
  - Checks cancelled, 1952 (Reel 935)
    Irving Trust regular and branch banks July, Sept.-Dec.; tab checks Jan.-Feb.
  - Checks cancelled, 1952 (Reel 936)
    Tab checks Feb.-Apr.
  - Checks cancelled, 1952 (Reel 937)
    Tab checks Apr.-July
  - Checks cancelled, 1952 (Reel 938)
    Tab checks July-Oct.
  - Checks cancelled, 1952 (Reel 939)
    Tab checks Oct.-Dec.
- Petty Cash, 1949-1954; 2
  - Petty cash, 1950 (Reel 632)
  - Petty cash billable, 1949 (Reel 528)
  - Petty cash billable, 1949 (Reel 533)
  - Petty cash billable, 1949 (Reel 534)
  - Petty cash billable, 1951 (Reel 534)
  - Petty cash billable, 1951 (Reel 542)
  - Petty cash billable, 1951 (Reel 544)
  - Petty cash billable, 1951 (Reel 554)
  - Petty cash billable, 1951-1952 (Reel 581)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 584)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 599)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 628)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 634)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 637)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 641)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 651)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 653)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 656)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 671)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 683)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 692)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 693)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 696)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 698)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 702)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 706)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 714)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 715)
    Ford truck direct mail; Ford Hi-Lo
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 721)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 723)
    Miscellaneous; Kraft TV
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 730)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 750)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 768)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 772)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 774)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 778)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 779)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 780)
    384-539 plus 95, 423, 424, 523, 524-535; Detroit expense; general journal (Douglas); Sept. 1952 1-21: miscellaneous, radio and television production talent, publicity, receivables 22-82/83 (72-76 missing)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 781)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 782)
  - Petty cash billable, 1952 (Reel 784)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 787)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 790)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 796)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 797)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 807)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 809)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 812)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 813)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 814)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 818)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 825)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 833)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 835)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 838)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 842)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 847)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 855)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 859)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 862)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 866)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 867)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 881)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 884)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 885)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 886)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 889)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 890)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 893)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 894)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 898)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 899)
  - Petty cash billable, 1953 (Reel 901)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 902)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 904)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 905)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 907)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 914)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 916)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 918)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 920)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 921)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 924)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 927)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 931)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 935)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 938)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 947)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 951)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 957)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 961)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 963)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 964)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 965)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 966)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 967)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 969)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 971)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 972)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 973)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 974)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 975)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 977)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 978)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 979)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 981)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 982)
  - Petty cash billable, 1954 (Reel 983)
  - petty cash miscellaneous, 1951 (Reel 533)
  - petty cash miscellaneous, 1951 (Reel 534)
  - Petty cash vouchers, 1951 (Reel 449)
  - Petty cash vouchers, 1951 (Reel 450)
- Production Billing, 1942-1953; 3
  - Production bill journal, 1947 (Reel 353)
  - Production billing, 1952 (Reel 785)
    296-491
  - Production billing, 1952 (Reel 786)
    491-708
  - Production billing, 1952 (Reel 787)
    708-end (production journal)
  - Production billing, 1953 (Reel 784)
    131-296
  - Production billing, new project, 1952 (Reel 778)
    Records in numbered envelopes 1-172; number 12 and 95 missing, 51 misfiled with the 70s
  - Production billing carbons, 1944 (Reel 410)
    Miscellaneous; New York sundries; P. Lorillard; Mentholatum; Northam Warren (Odorono, Cutex); Owens-Illinois Glass; Lever Brothers (Vimms); RCA
  - Production billing carbons, 1944 (Reel 411)
    RCA; Reader's Digest Association; Rheem Research Products; Shell Oil (West Coast); Skol; Putnam Trust of Greenwich; Reader's Digest international edition; Standard Brands; United Church Canvass; United Cut Flowers; Universal Pictures; U.S. Playing Card; U.S. Lines; War Advertising Council; Ward Baking; J.B. Williams; U.S. Lines; Webb Young Trader; W.F. Young (Absorbine Jr.); Kodak
  - Production billing carbons, 1946 (Reel 378)
    Standard Brands: Chase & Sanborn; Fleischmann's Yeast
  - Production billing carbons, 1946 (Reel 379)
    Standard Brands (Royal, Stox); Textron; U.S. Brewers Foundation; United Cut Flowers; U.S. Lines; U.S. Playing Card; Universal Pictures; Vimms; Mentholatum; Cutex; Western Union; J.B. Williams; W.F. Young; Webb Young; miscellaneous
  - Production billing carbons, 1948 (Reel 412)
    Kodak; Ford; Ford Dealers Advertising Association
  - Production billing carbons, 1948 (Reel 413)
    Ford Dealers Advertising Association; petty cash vouchers
  - Production billing carbons, 1948 (Reel 414)
    Ford; Ford Dealers
  - Production billing carbons, 1949 (Reel 693)
    Ford; Ford Dealer
  - Production billing carbons, 1949 (Reel 694)
    Ford Dealer
  - Production billing carbons, 1949-1950 (Reel 695)
    Ford Dealer; American Weekly; Anthracite Institute; Asphalt Tile Institute; Atlantic Refining; Atlantis Sales; Ballantine
  - Production billing carbons, 1950 (Reel 692)
    Ford
  - Production billing carbons, 1950 (Reel 696)
    Berkshire; Brillo; Buxton; Carreras; Carter's Ink; Caterpillar; Devoe & Raynolds; Champion; Eastman Kodak
  - Production billing carbons, 1950 (Reel 697)
    Eastman Kodak; Fanny Farmer; Farrell Lines; Florida Citrus Commission; General Cigar; Institute of Life Insurance; John Irving Shoe; Irving Trust; Johns-Manville; Kroy Wool Processors; Lever; Committee for Community Auto Rates; Massachussetts Mutual; Metropolitan Motor Coach; Mentholatum; Michigan Hospital Service; NBC; National Fisheries Institute; New Holland Machine; Oneida; Owens-Illinois Glass; Oxford University Press
  - Production billing carbons, 1950 (Reel 698)
    Oxford University Press; Pacific Mills; Pan Am; Penick & Ford; Pepsodent (Rayve); Pharma-Craft; Pond's; Purolator; RCA
  - Production billing carbons, 1950 (Reel 699)
    RCA; Reader's Digest; Rototiller; Rystan; Scott Paper
  - Production billing carbons, 1950 (Reel 700)
    Scott Paper; Shell Oil; Scranton Lace; Squibb; Standard Brands; Staze; Textron; U.S. Lines; United Artists; U.S. Playing Card; Ward Baking; Western Union; J.B. Williams; W.F. Young; Webb Young Trader; New York sundries
  - Production billing carbons, 1950 (Reel 701)
    New York sundries; New York financial; Ford Dealer Association
  - Production billing carbons, 1950 (Reel 702)
    Ford Dealer Association
  - Production billing carbons, 1950 (Reel 703)
    Ford Dealer Association; Ford Motor
  - Production billing carbons, 1950 (Reel 706)
    Swift; Trailer Coach Manufacturers; Weco Products; Chicago sundries
  - Production billing carbons, California, 1945 (Reel 304)
    NBC
  - Production billing carbons, California, 1947 (Reel 353)
    Extras for November
  - Production billing carbons, California and Chicago, 1944 (Reel 297)
    California: starting with Safeway Stores; Chicago: Weco
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago, 1945-1946 (Reel 327)
    Ford; Ford Rocky Mountains; Illinois Power; Kent Products; Kraft; Libby McNeil & Libby; Millers National Federation; National Dairy Products; New York Subway; Noma Inc.; Norther Trust; Parker Pen; Public Health Institute; Science Associates; Seven-Up
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago, 1947 (Reel 351)
    Libby McNeil & Libby; Millers National Federation; National Association of Independent Tire Dealers; National Dairy Products; New York Subways; Northern Trust; Parker Pen; Safeway Stores; Science Association; Seven-Up; Standard Fabrications; Storkline Furniture; Sundries; Swift
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago, 1948 (Reel 400)
    Kraft; Lever Brothers; Libby McNeil & Libby petty cash vouchers; Millers National Federation; National Dairy Products Co.; New York Subways; Northern Trust; Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance; Parker Pen; Seven-Up; Weco Products; Window Shade Institute
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago, 1949-1950 (Reel 440)
    Kraft; petty cash vouchers; Libby McNeil & Libby; Millers National Federation; National Dairy Products Co.; New York Subways; Northern Trust; Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance; Parker Pen; Rayve Home Permanent
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago, 1949-1950 (Reel 441)
    Rayve Home Permanent; Pepsodent; petty cash vouchers; Safeway; Kitchen Craft Flour (Famous Flours); Seven-Up; Shellmar Products; Storkline Furniture; Swift; petty cash vouchers; Trailer Coach Manufacturers Association; Vono Ltd.; Window Shade Institute; Weco Products
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago, 1950 (Reel 705)
    Kraft; Libby McNeil & Libby; Millers National Foundation; Northern Trust; Northwestern Mutual; Parker Pen; Seven-Up; Shellmar; Storkline Furniture; Swift
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago, 1951 (Reel 768)
    Arnold Schwinn; Borg-Warner; Bowman Dairy; Famous Flours; Elgin; Indiana Bell Telephone; International Minerals and Chemical; Kraft
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago, 1951 (Reel 769)
    Kraft; Libby; Metropolitan Housing and Planning Council; Millers National Foundation; National Trailways; Northern Trust; Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance; Parker Pen; Shellmar; Seven-Up; Swift
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago, 1951 (Reel 770)
    Swift; Trailer Coach Manufacturers; Weco Products; West Coast
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago, 1953 (Reel 922)
    Borg-Warner; Bowman Dairy; Carolina Coach; Chicago Show Printing; Credit Union; Famous Flours; Fund for Adult Education; Illinois State Chamber of Commerce; Indiana Bell Telephone; Kraft; Indiana Motor Truck Association; Libby McNeil & Libby; Northern Trust; Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance; Parker Pen; Quaker Oats
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago, 1953 (Reel 923)
    Quaker Oats; Arnold Schwinn; Seven-Up; Sophie May Candy; Sta-Nu; Swift; Trailer Coach Manufacturers Association; Union Stock Yards; Weco Products
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago and California, 1945 (Reel 303)
    Chicago: Libby McNeil & Libby; California: NBC
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago and California, 1947 (Reel 352)
    Chicago: Swift; Verifine Foods; Weco Products; California: Apparel Inc.; Arizona Grapefruit Program Committee; Bateman-Richler; Bechtel International; Boyle-Midway; Calavo Growers of California; California Baking (Langendorf); California Desert Grapefruit Industry Board; California Lima Bean Growers Association; Cruttendon & Co.; Design Associates; Douglas Aircraft; Garrett Corp.; Erle P. Halliburton; Hanford Milk; J.T. Hardeman Hat Co.; Holly Sugar; Hollywood Reporter; Hotel Last Frontier Las Vegas; Kaiser Fleetwings; Kraft; Las Vegas Nevada Chamber of Commerce; Lawrence Warehouse; Los Angeles Times Mirror; Mabs of Hollywood; McClatchy Broadcasting; Panama Pacific Line; RCA Victor Division; Leo J. Meyberg; Mutual Orange Distributions; Northrop Aircraft; Puget Sound Navigation; Safeway Stores; Skyway International Luggage; Spreckels Sugar; Sunset Magazine; Swift; Threkald; Television Distributors of Southern California; Trolls; United Artists; Washington State Apples; Western Growers Association; Wine Advisory Board
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago and New York, 1942 (Reel 285)
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago and New York, 1942 (Reel 286)
    After Ballentine, see 3 bills (Chicago) Bauer & Black; New York Office through Lamont-Corliss
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago and New York, 1943 (Reel 289)
    Chicago starting with Swift; New York
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago and New York, 1944 (Reel 293)
    Chicago: Kraft; New York: Financial
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago and New York, 1942-1943 (Reel 288)
    New York: Fulton (?) Trust; Chicago through Seven-Up
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago and New York, 1943-1944 (Reel 292)
    New York: Sharp & Dohme; Chicago: Kraft
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago and New York, 1944-1945 (Reel 298)
    Chicago: Weco; New York: Window Shade Institute, Financial
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago and New York, 1946-1947 (Reel 339)
    Chicago: Seven-Up; Storkline Furniture; Swift; Toni; Union Central Life Insurance; Weco; James D. Woolf (Navajo Silvercraft); New York: American Weekly; Anthracite Institute; Ariston; Fred Astaire Dance Studios; Atlantis Sales; P. Ballantine; Brame-Domar Motors; Brillo; Buxton; Carter's Ink; Kodak
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago and New York, 1951 (Reel 771)
    West Coast; New York: American Weekly; Atlantis Sales; Anthracite Institute; Ballantine; Brillo; Buxton; Carreras; Carter's Ink; Carter's Products; Caterpillar; Champion Spark Plug; Church & Dwight
  - Production billing carbons, Chicago and West Coast, 1952 (Reel 899)
    Chicago: Libby McNeil & Libby; National Trailways; Northern Trust; Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance; Parker Pen; Seven-Up; Sophie May Candy; Sta-Nu; Swift; Trailer Coach Manufacturers Association; Weco Products; West Coast: Bishop-Conklin; California Lima Bean; California Raisin Advisory Board; Douglas Aircraft; Eisenhower-Nixon campaign; Northwest Ford Dealers (Seattle); Ford Dealers (San Francisco, Los Angeles, San Marino); Friden Calculating Machings; Garrett
  - Production billing carbons, Detroit, 1951 (Reel 886)
  - Production billing carbons, Detroit, 1951 (Reel 887)
    Ford Dealer Association, Ford Motor
  - Production billing carbons, Detroit, 1952 (Reel 896)
  - Production billing carbons, Detroit, 1952 (Reel 897)
    Ford Dealer Association, Ford Motor, Ford direct mail
  - Production billing carbons, Detroit and Chicago, 1950 (Reel 704)
    Ford direct mail service; Chicago: Borg-Warner; Bowman Dairy; E.J. Brach; Elgin; Famous Flours; Indiana Bell Telephone; International Minerals and Chemical
  - Production billing carbons, Detroit and Chicago, 1952 (Reel 898)
    Detroit: Ford; Chicago: American Trucking; Arnold Schwinn; Borg-Warner (Norge); Bowman Dairy; Chicago Heart Association; Citizen's Traffic Safety Board; Credit Union National Association; Famous Flours; Fund for Adult Education; Indiana Bell Telephone; Kraft; Libby McNeil & Libby
  - Production billing carbons, Detroit and New York, 1951-1952 (Reel 888)
    Detroit: Ford, Ford Dealer; New York: Atlantis Sales; Associated Hospital Service; Anthracite Institute; Ballantine; Berkshire Fine Spinning Association; Bio Research; Brillo; Burroughs Adding Machine
  - Production billing carbons, Detroit and New York, 1952-1953 (Reel 915)
    Fleischmann's Yeast; Ford Dealers; New York: Atlantis Sales; Ballantine; Brillo; Burroughs Adding Machine
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1942 (Reel 287)
    Lamont-Corliss
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1943 (Reel 290)
    Brewing Industry Foundation; Lamont-Corliss
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1943 (Reel 291)
    Lamont-Corliss; more Lamont-Corliss and Lorillard after Pan-American; Sharp & Dohme
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1944 (Reel 294)
    Financial; through Lux, American Weekly, Atlantis Sales; Ballantine
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1944 (Reel 295)
    Ballantine; Block Drug; Brewing Industry Foundation; Irving Trust; Johns-Manville; National Broadcasting-on a;phabetical run`
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1945 (Reel 299)
    Financial from Sept.; Atlantis Sales after Institute of Life; Kraft
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1945 (Reel 300)
    Kraft, Reynolds
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1945 (Reel 301)
    Reynolds Metals, sundries
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1946 (Reel 305)
    Absorbine Jr.; "Happy Endings" sample radio script by John A. Carter; Reader's Digest; Shell; P. Ballantine & Sons "His Honor the Barber" by Barry Fitzgerald; U.S. Brewers Foundation; Eastman Kodak spots Feb. through Dec.; Fanny Farmer Candies; Ford Motor Company: "Bob Crosby Show" and "The Ford Show"
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1946 (Reel 320)
    Fanny Farmer; American Weekly; Anthracite Institute; Atlantis Sales; P. Ballantine; Brillo; Buxton; Carter's Ink; Kodak
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1946 (Reel 321)
    Fanny Farmer; Ford; Ford Dealer
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1946 (Reel 322)
    Ford Dealer; General Cigar; Gillette; Arthur Guinness; Associated Hospital Service; Institute of Life Insurance; Ford; Irving Trust; Johns-Manville; Kellogg; Lamont-Corliss; Lever Brothers (Lux Flakes)
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1946 (Reel 323)
    Lever Brothers (Lux Flakes, Lux Pearls); Massachusetts Hospital Service; Mentholatum; National Broadcasting Company; Omega Watch; Owens-Illinois Glass; Oxford University Press; Pan-American Airways
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1945 (Reel 431)
    Lamont Corliss; Pond's Extract; Lever Brothers (Lux Flakes, Lux Toilet Soap); Massachusetts Hospital Service; Mentholatum; National Broadcasting
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1945-1949 (Reel 432)
    NBC; Owens-Illinois Glass; Pan Am; Northern Trust; American Weekly; Anthracite Intsitute; Atlantic Refining; Atlantis Sales; P. Ballantine
  - Production billing carbons, New York, 1946 (Reel 324)